Historical Photograph Collection: Glass-Plate Negatives Series, 1880-1920: Preliminary Finding Aid AC317
University Archives
- Buildings and Grounds, 1811-1944; 71 boxes
  - Nassau Hall, 1900-1920; 9 boxes
    - Corner of Nassau Hall near library, 1919, 1 box (Box 47)
      Original sleeve No. 408
      Plate number: 903
    - Tigers of Nassau Hall in winter of 1918, 1 box (Box 56)
      Original sleeve No. 1066
      Plate number: 1072
    - Nassau Hall and students, Undated; 1 box (Box 110)
      Plate number: 376
  - Palmer Lab, 1907-1908; 6 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Palmer Lab, including its construction in 1907-1908.
    No arrangement action taken at the time of processing. Some glass plates are numbered and correspond to numbered prints in boxes 114 and 115 of this collection.
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Undated; 3 boxes (Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
      Paper print 1-60
      Plate number: 178, 210, 234-237, 256-258, 261, 263-269, 288-290, 292-293, 299, 301-303, 423-428, 544-45, 548-549, 553, 555, 556-557, 561-565 and unnumbered
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Dec 16, 1907, 1 box (Box 3)
      No paper print. 61
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Dec. 9, 1907, 1 box (Box 3)
      No paper print. 62
      Plate number: 452
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Dec. 16, 1907, 1 box (Box 3)
      No paper print. 63
      Plate number: 453
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Dec. 24, 1907, 1 box (Box 3)
      No paper print. 64
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Jan. 6, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 65. R2721
      Plate number: 291
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Feb. 17, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 66. R2728
      Plate number: 298
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Feb. 17, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 67. R2726
      Plate number: 296
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Feb. 20, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 68. R2730
      Plate number: 300
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Feb. 25, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 69. R4536
    - Palmer Lab Construction, March 2, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 70. R4537
    - Palmer Lab Construction, March 9, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 71. R4533
    - Palmer Lab Construction, March 9, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 72. R4535
    - Palmer Lab Construction, March 9, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 73. R4538
    - Palmer Lab Construction, March 16, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 74. R2602
    - Palmer Lab Construction, March 24, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 75. R2600
      Plate number: 171
    - Palmer Lab Construction, March 24, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 76. R2601
      Plate number: 172
    - Palmer Lab Construction, March 30, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 77. R2598
      Plate number: 170
    - Palmer Lab Construction, March 30, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 78. R2603
    - Palmer Lab Construction, April 2, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 79. R2597
      Plate number: 169
    - Palmer Lab Construction, April 13, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 80. R4545
    - Palmer Lab Construction, April 20, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 81. R4529
    - Palmer Lab Construction, April 28, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 82. R4528
    - Palmer Lab Construction, May 4, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 83. R4253
    - Palmer Lab Construction, May 25, 1908, 1 box (Box 4)
      No paper print. 84. R4542
    - Palmer Lab Construction, July 6, 1908, 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 85. R5658
      Plate number: 552
    - Palmer Lab Construction, July 20, 1908, 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 86. R2580
      Plate number: 154
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Dec. 1907?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 87. R2415
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Jan 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 88. R2413
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Feb. 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 89. R2727
      Plate number: 297
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Mar.-Apr. 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 90. R2599
      Plate number: 170 A
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Mar.-Apr. 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 91. R4540
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Mar.-Apr. 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 92. R4543
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Mar.-Apr. 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 93. R4532
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Mar.-Apr. 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 94. R4530
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Mar.-Apr. 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 95. R4549
    - Palmer Lab Construction, Mar.-Apr. 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 96. 4544
    - Palmer Lab Construction, April-May 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 97. R4548
    - Palmer Lab Construction, April-May 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 98. R5653
      Plate number: 547
    - Palmer Lab Construction, June 15, 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 99. R4516
    - Palmer Lab Construction, June 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 100. R5656
      Plate number: 550
    - Palmer Lab Construction, June 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 101. R2690
      Plate number: 260
    - Palmer Lab Construction, June 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 102. R5660
      Plate number: 554
    - Palmer Lab Construction, June 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 103. R5657
      Plate number: 551
    - Palmer Lab Construction, July 1908?, circa 1908; 1 box (Box 5)
      No paper print. 104. R2588
      Plate number: 161
    - Palmer Lab: front door and west wing, no statues in niches, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 218
  - Palmer Stadium, 1920; 4 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Palmer Stadium.
    - Palmer Stadium, Undated; 1 box (Box 14)
      Plate number: 295
    - Palmer Stadium, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 490
    - Palmer Stadium, from south, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 491
    - Palmer Stadium football game, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 492-495
    - Palmer Stadium, part of crowd on field, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 496
    - Palmer Stadium from outside on day of Yale game, 1920, 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 427
      Plate number: 922
    - Buildings and grounds, Palmer Stadium, between halves Yale vs. Princeton, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1261
  - Patton Hall, 1906; 7 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Patton Hall.
    - Patton Hall, from southwest, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 145
    - Patton Hall showing plaque, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 220
    - Patton Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 219
    - Patton Hall, east facade, just finished and no landscaping, 1906; 1 box (Box 16)
      Plate number: 313
    - Patton, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 498-499
    - Last entry of Patton Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 48)
      Original sleeve No. 422
      Plate number: 917
    - Last entry of Patton Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 434
      Plate number: 929
  - Princeton Cemetery, undated; 4 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Princeton Cemetery, including the tombs of Grover Cleveland, Ruth Cleveland, Aaron Burr, and James McCosh.
    - Cemetery, presidents' graves, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 413
    - Aaron Burr Jr. tombstone, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 394
    - Tomb of Grover Cleveland in Princeton cemetery, Undated; 1 box (Box 32)
      Original sleeve No. 115
      Plate number: 646
    - Tombs of Grover and Ruth Cleveland in Princeton cemetery, Undated; 1 box (Box 32)
      Original sleeve No. 116
      Plate number: 647
    - Tomb of Aaron Burr in Princeton cemetery, Undated; 1 box (Box 32)
      Original sleeve No. 117
      Plate number: 648
    - Tombs of Presidents of the University and Aaron Burr in Princeton cemetery, Undated; 1 box (Box 32)
      Original sleeve No. 118
      Plate number: 649
    - Tomb of President McCosh in Princeton cemetery, Undated; 1 box (Box 32)
      Original sleeve No. 119
      Plate number: 650
    - cemetery, grave stone of Aaron Burr, V. Pres 1801-1805, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
    - cemetery, Undated; 1 box (Box 98)
  - Princeton Inn, 1919; 3 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show images of the Princeton Inn.
    - Princeton Inn, from golf course, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 146
    - Princeton Inn, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 222
    - Princeton Inn from golf course, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 221
    - Princeton Inn on golf course, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 500
  - Proctor Hall, 1923; 1 box
    Glass plates within this subseries show images of Proctor Hall.
    - Stained glass window, Proctor Hall, 1923, 1 box (Box 54)
      Original sleeve No. 665
      Plate number: 1018
    - Organ loft of Proctor Hall, G.C., 1923, 1 box (Box 54)
      Original sleeve No. 666
      Plate number: 1019
  - Prospect, 1919; 10 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show images of Prospect House, Prospect Street, and Prospect Garden.
    - Prospect Garden, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 147
    - Prospect Gate, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 223
    - McCosh House on Prospect Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 13)
      Plate number: 286
    - Prospect Garden, Undated; 1 box (Box 14)
      Plate number: 296-297
    - Prospect Garden, Undated; 1 box (Box 16)
      Plate number: 314
    - Prospect, Undated; 1 box (Box 23)
      Plate number: 390
    - Prospect, north facade, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 501-502
    - Prospect and garden, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 503-507
    - Prospect Ave. from '79 Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 508
    - 79 Hall from Prospect Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 517
    - 1879 hall arch, looking toward Prospect, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 124
    - Pospect from Prospect gardens, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 432
      Plate number: 927
    - Entrance to Prospect, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 433
      Plate number: 928
    - Views of Prospect Garden, Undated; 1 box (Box 100)
    - No Description Available, Undated; 1 box (Box 100)
  - Pyne Hall and Library, 1916; 6 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show images of the Pyne Hall and Library.
    - Christian student with Pyne Library, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 119
    - Pyne Hall, late construction, from north, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 148
    - Pyne Hall, just finished, no landscaping, broken memorial in background, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 149
    - Pyne Hall courtyard, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 150
    - Pyne Library, south and west facades, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 151
    - Pyne Library, tower from west, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 225
    - Pyne Library, tower and arch looking west, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 224
    - Pyne Hall courtyard with people, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 509
    - Pyne Library, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 510
    - Upper Pyne with horse and carriage and people, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 527
    - Buildings and grounds, Pyne Library in winter, Jan. 1916, circa 1916; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1264
    - Pyne courtyard, Undated; 1 box (Box 110)
      Plate number: 375
  - Reunion Hall, undated; 2 boxes
    This subseries shows images of Reunion Hall.
    - Reunion, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 513
    - Reunion Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 111)
      Plate number: 370
  - Seminary, undated; 2 boxes
    This subseries shows views of Princeton Theological Seminary.
    - Seminary, Lenox Library, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 157
    - Seminary, Lenox Library, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 514
    - Seminary, Stuart, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 515
    - Seminary, Brown, Cleveland Tower in background, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 516
  - Stereopticon, undated; 1 box
    This subseries consists of a collection stereopticon images.
    - Stereopticon, Bonner-Marquand gym, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1127
    - Stereopticon, campus view, front campus, Chancellor Green, Old Chapel, Whig, Nassau Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Print in small photo file (Campus Views)
      Plate number: 1128
    - Stereopticon, campus view, front campus, John C. Green School of Science, Dickinson, Chancellor Green, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1129
    - Stereopticon, campus view, Bonner-Marquand gym, Reunion, West, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1130
    - Stereopticon, campus view, Stanhope, part of Reunion, Bonner-Marquand gym and Halsted Observatory in background, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1131
    - Stereopticon, dining hall (University Hall?), Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1132
    - Stereopticon, East College, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Print in small photo file
      Plate number: 1133
    - Stereopticon, E.M. Museum, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1134-1136
    - Stereopticon, MaClean House, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1137
    - Stereopticon, Nassau Hall and Cannon Green, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1138
    - Stereopticon, Reunion from Cannon Green, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1139
    - Stereopticon, John C. Green School of Science, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1140
    - Stereopticon, Witherspoon Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1141
    - Stereopticon, West College, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1142
    - Stereopticon, Witherspoon Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 59)
      Plate number: 1143
  - Town Views, 1900; 15 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show Princeton Town.
    Some plates lack description and may be unrelated.
    - Town, pre Palmer Square, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 159
    - Town, pre Palmer Square, Holder Tower, right background, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 160
    - Town, behind Nassau Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
    - Town alley, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 162
    - Town, pre Palmer Square, Holder Tower, center background, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 163
    - Town, Undated; 1 box (Box 7)
      Plate number: 164-165
    - Town, pre Palmer Square?, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 166
    - Town, Nassau Street looking east, circa 1900; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 227
    - Nassau Street, Carpenter Hall, 39 & 41, Undated; 1 box (Box 10)
      Plate number: 217
    - Town, catalpa trees in front of Morven, Undated; 1 box (Box 11)
      Plate number: 321
    - Nassau Inn, Palmer Square, Undated; 1 box (Box 13)
      Plate number: 292-293
    - Palmer Square west and playhouse, before tiger installed, Undated; 1 box (Box 14)
      Plate number: 294
    - Broad Mead, early, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 404
    - Broad Mead, from north with gates, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 405
    - Palmer Square, west and north, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 488
    - Nassau Street, houses south side, Undated; 1 box (Box 26)
      Plate number: 489
    - Stony Brook bridge, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 518
    - Catalpa trees along Stockton Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 438
      Plate number: 933
    - Bridge over Stony Brook on Mercer Street, Undated; 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1099
      Plate number: 1098
    - Train station, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Old train station, Undated; 1 box (Box 99)
    - Harrison Street bridge, Nov. 7, Undated; 1 box (Box 102)
    - Harrison Street bridge, Nov. 8, Undated; 1 box (Box 102)
    - No Description Available, Undated; 1 box (Box 102)
    - No Description Available, Undated; 1 box (Box 102)
  - Unidentified Buildings and Grounds, undated; 10 boxes
    This subseries contains glass plates that have not yet been identified by a specific structure or site, on or around the Princeton University Campus.
    - 36 Buildings on one plate, Undated; 1 box (Box 9)
      Plate number: 234
    - 36 buildings and scenes, Undated; 1 box (Box 14)
    - Door, Undated; 1 box (Box 60)
      Plate number: 1169
    - Princeton?, Undated; 1 box (Box 60)
      Plate number: 1170
    - Large monument, decoration for celebration, Undated; 1 box (Box 95)
    - Stone arched entrance with stained glass, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Large woodshop, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Reading room?, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Stable, man with cow, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Buildings, people, bicycle, pathways, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Castle like building and steeple, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Castle turrets, Undated; 1 box (Box 96)
    - Park scene, four men seated on bench, two men standing in costumes, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
    - Closeup of masonry, yardstick with local advertising, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
    - Buildings, parks, square, Undated; 1 box (Box 98)
    - Library (stacks of books), Undated; 1 box (Box 98)
    - Building, Undated; 1 box (Box 98)
    - Portraits on wall, Undated; 1 box (Box 99)
    - Stone cottage, Undated; 1 box (Box 99)
      8x5
    - Building towers, Undated; 1 box (Box 99)
    - Walkway with gentlemen, Undated; 1 box (Box 99)
    - Appears to be a pool, Undated; 1 box (Box 99)
    - No Description Available, Undated; 2 boxes (Box 99, Box 100)
    - Close up of masonry, Undated; 1 box (Box 101)
  - University Field, undated; 4 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show images of University Field.
    - University Field, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 523
    - University Field football game, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 524-525
    - University Field, Undated; 1 box (Box 19)
      Plate number: 338
    - Tigers guarding entrance to univ. field from the west, Undated; 1 box (Box 52)
      Original sleeve No. 479-480
      Plate number: 981-982
    - Tigers guarding entrance to univ. field from the east, Undated; 1 box (Box 52)
      Original sleeve No. 481
      Plate number: 983
    - Grand stands with crowd, Undated; 1 box (Box 97)
  - University Hall, 1900; 3 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show University Hall.
    - University Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 167
    - University Hall, circa 1900; 1 box (Box 16)
      Plate number: 315
    - University Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 526
  - University Power Company, undated; 7 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show images of the University Power Company.
    - University Power Co., interior, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)
      Plate number: 168-172
    - No Description Available, Undated; 1 box (Box 74)
      Plate number: 1403-1405
    - Laboratory?, Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
      Plate number: 1406, 1417-1418
    - University Power Comapny, Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
    - Powerhouse?, Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
    - University Power Company, Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
      Plate number: 1411-1413
    - Printing plant, Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
    - Powerhouse?, Undated; 1 box (Box 75)
    - No Description Available, Undated; 4 boxes (Box 76, Box 77, Box 78, Box 79)
  - Whig and Clio, undated; 5 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show images of Whig and Clio.
    - Ditch being dug between West and Clio, looking north, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 122
    - Ditch being dug between West and Clio, looking south, Undated; 1 box (Box 6)
      Plate number: 123
    - Clio, Undated; 1 box (Box 24)
      Plate number: 423-424
    - Whig, photo of a painting, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 529
    - Whig, Undated; 1 box (Box 27)
      Plate number: 530-532
    - Clio Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 48)
      Original sleeve No. 417
      Plate number: 912
    - Whig Hall and class, Undated; 1 box (Box 109)
      Plate number: 373-374
  - Winter Scenes, 1917-1920; 7 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show the campus grounds and buildings in winter.
    - Sleet storm in Princeton, winter of 1919, 1 box (Box 31)
      Original sleeve No. 99
      Plate number: 630
    - Front campus and library in winter of 1917-18, 1917-1918; 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 390
      Plate number: 885
    - Road between Dod ad Edwards in winter, 1918, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 391. (Pic cover)
      Plate number: 886
    - Chancelor Green library in winter, 1918, 1 box (Box 46)
      Original sleeve No. 393
      Plate number: 888
    - Ice storm in 1920, Prospect Street, 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 442
      Plate number: 938
    - The front of Prospect in an ice storm in 1920, 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 443
      Plate number: 939
    - Buyot Hall in ice storm, 1920, 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 444
      Plate number: 940
    - Blair Hall arch in the winter time, 1919, 1 box (Box 49)
      Original sleeve No. 441
      Plate number: 936
    - Witherspoon Hall in ice storm, 1920, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 445
      Plate number: 941
    - Lombardy poplars and canal in winter of 1919-1920, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 446
      Plate number: 942
    - West side of Palmer Lab in the winter, Undated; 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 450
      Plate number: 946
    - Student volunteer statue in winter of 1919, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 455
      Plate number: 951
    - Washington Road bridge over Carnegie Lake in winter of 1919, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 457
      Plate number: 953
    - Old apple tree and Guyot Hall in winter of 1919, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 453
      Plate number: 949
    - Old apple tree and Guyot Hall in winter of 1919, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 459
      Plate number: 955
    - Evergreen trees on Path between Prospect and Guyot Hall in winter, Undated; 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 451
      Plate number: 947
    - Looking toward Patton Hall from Prospect, winter of 1919, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 452
      Plate number: 948
    - The tower of Prospect through evergreen trees, winter if 1919, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 454
      Plate number: 950
    - Entrance to Prospect in winter of 1919, 1 box (Box 50)
      Original sleeve No. 456
      Plate number: 952
    - Interior of library court in winter, Undated; 1 box (Box 57)
      Original sleeve No. 1100
      Plate number: 1099
    - Princeton front campus in winter of 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
      Original sleeve No. 1118
      Plate number: 1116
    - Snow covered tree on front campus, 1917, 1 box (Box 58)
      Original sleeve No. 1124
      Plate number: 1122
    - Buildings and grounds, Prospect in winter, 1st view, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1262
    - Buildings and grounds, Prospect in winter, 2nd view, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1263
    - Buildings and grounds, Stony Brook in winter near Carnegie Lake, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1265
    - Buildings and grounds, Stony Brook in winter, Undated; 1 box (Box 65)
      Plate number: 1266
  - Witherspoon Hall, undated; 3 boxes
    Glass plates within this subseries show images of Witherspoon Hall.
    - Witherspoon Hall, Undated; 1 box (Box 8)